<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>people on Beth&#39;s Genealogy Site</title>
    <link>/tags/people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in people on Beth&#39;s Genealogy Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Family test</title>
      <link>/posts/family-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/family-test/</guid>
      <description>On the other hand, we denounce with righteous indignation and dislike men who are so beguiled and demoralized by the charms of pleasure of the moment, so blinded by desire, that they cannot foresee the pain and trouble that are bound to ensue; and equal blame belongs to those who fail in their duty through weakness of will, which is the same as saying through shrinking from toil and pain. These cases are perfectly simple and easy to distinguish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fall</title>
      <link>/posts/the-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-fall/</guid>
      <description>“Men are never convinced of your reasons, of your sincerity, of the seriousness of your sufferings, except by your death. So long as you are alive, your case is doubtful; you have a right only to their skepticism.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Third post</title>
      <link>/posts/third-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/third-post/</guid>
      <description>Mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna mahna.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
