<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest Blog Posts on Beth&#39;s Genealogy Site</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Latest Blog Posts on Beth&#39;s Genealogy Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Basile - Tar for Mortar</title>
      <link>/posts/Jonathan-Basile-Tar-for-Mortar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/Jonathan-Basile-Tar-for-Mortar/</guid>
      <description>A text exists in what Borges calls an infinite dialogue with its recipients, and its endless recontextualization guarantees that even without a mark of difference every book, page, and even letter can differ from themselves. Our libraries do not fall short of universality because of a character we’ve left out, but because totality itself is essentially incomplete.
Tar for Mortar</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sea Was as Wet as Wet Can Be</title>
      <link>/posts/The-Sea-Was-as-Wet-as-Wet-Can-Be/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 1967 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/The-Sea-Was-as-Wet-as-Wet-Can-Be/</guid>
      <description>I said her name once more, just for the record, and then I stood and turned from them and walked to the bluff. I rounded the bluff and the beach stretched before me, vast, smooth, empty, and remote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project No. 1</title>
      <link>/posts/Project-No.-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 1966 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/Project-No.-1/</guid>
      <description>For a moment she&#39;d wondered if the seal around her sockets were tight enough to allow the tears simply to go on and fill up the entire lens space and never dry. She could carry the sadness of the moment with her that way forever, see the world refracted through those tears, those specific tears, as if indices as yet unfound varied in important ways from cry to cry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Chute</title>
      <link>/posts/La-Chute/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 1956 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/La-Chute/</guid>
      <description>“Men are never convinced of your reasons, of your sincerity, of the seriousness of your sufferings, except by your death. So long as you are alive, your case is doubtful; you have a right only to their skepticism.”</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
